Guide to the Gödel Editorial Project Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records, Accession ARCH-2008-054
  - Ulam – correspondence of editors (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Ulam (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - van Heijenoort – TeXscripts (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - van Heijenoort – photocopies of original correspondence (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - von Neumann – introductory note (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - von Neumann – TeXscripts (1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - von Neumann – TeXscripts (2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - von Neumann – typescripts (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - von Neumann – translations (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - von Neumann – photocopies of original correspondence (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Wang – correspondence of editors (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Wang – introductory note (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Wang – TeXscripts (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Wang – TeXscripts (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Wang – photocopies of original correspondence 1948-72 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Wang – photocopies of original correspondence 1972-75 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Wang – photocopies of original correspondence 1976-78 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Wang – references and Appendix B (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Zermelo (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Calendars of correspondence (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Proofreading inventory of Nachlass [finding aid to Gödel papers at Princeton] (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Appendix A – TeXscript (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Scott, Appendix A – photocopies of original correspondence (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Appendix B - TeXscript (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Textual notes - TeXscript (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Addenda and corrigenda (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - References – correspondence of editors (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - References – TeXscript (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - References – TeXscript (2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - References – additional material (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - References, Vol. IV, 1/31/02 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - References, Vol. IV, TeXscripts (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - References, Vol. IV, TeXscripts (2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Reference searching (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Editorial principles (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Headings list to Gödel's notebooks and record of transcriptions (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Reports (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Reports (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Reviews (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Lists for microfilming book annotations (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Preservation Resources (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Microfilming correspondence, 1996-97 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Microfilming correspondence and other records, 1989-95 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Permission letter for photocopying from Gödel's Nachlass 1997 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence re microfilm publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Final version of finding aid to Gödel's papers at Princeton (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Microfilming correspondence, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Microfilming correspondence, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Committee correspondence (1 of 2) 1996 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Committee correspondence (2 of 2) 1995-96 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Firestone Library correspondence, 1985-89 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Meeting minutes, 1988-2000 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Volume III, general correspondence, 1994-97 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Volume III, general correspondence, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Volume III, general correspondence, 1987-93 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Volume IV, general correspondence, 1993-2001 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Vol. IV, index – corrected text (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Vol. IV, corrections to first unified copy, preface to p. 345 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Vol. IV, corrections to first unified copy, p. 346-end (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Vol. IV, final batch of corrections, to p. 256 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Vol. IV, final batch of corrections, p. 257-564 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Vol. IV, final batch of corrections, references and addenda (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Vol. IV-V, CD of complete computer files (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Vol. IV final copy [in box] (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Vol. IV final copy [in box] (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Vol. V – corrections to first combined version, preface-p. 251 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Vol. V – corrections to first combined version, p. 255-end (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Vol. V – final corrections (1 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Vol. V – final corrections (2 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Vol. V – final corrections 12/1/02 (1 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Vol. V – final corrections 12/1/02 (2 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 6)